export const chapter = "Chapter - 7: Delhi : The Heart of India  ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What river does Delhi lie west of?",
        optionA: "Ganges",
        optionB: "Yamuna",
        optionC: "Brahmaputra",
        correctAnswer: "Yamuna",
      },
      {
        question: "Which two neighboring states border Delhi?",
        optionA: "Rajasthan and Punjab",
        optionB: "Uttar Pradesh and Haryana",
        optionC: "Madhya Pradesh and Himachal Pradesh",
        correctAnswer: "Uttar Pradesh and Haryana",
      },
      {
        question: "Who built his capital at Delhi, calling it Shahjahanabad?",
        optionA: "Akbar",
        optionB: "Shah Jahan",
        optionC: "Aurangzeb",
        correctAnswer: "Shah Jahan",
      },
      {
        question: "Which part of Delhi is now referred to as Old Delhi?",
        optionA: "New Delhi",
        optionB: "Mughal Delhi",
        optionC: "Shahjahanabad",
        correctAnswer: "Shahjahanabad",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who built New Delhi when they shifted their capital to Delhi from Kolkata?",
        optionA: "The Mughals",
        optionB: "The British",
        optionC: "The French",
        correctAnswer: "The British",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What are some of the satellite cities incorporated into the National Capital Territory of Delhi?",
        optionA: "Agra and Jaipur",
        optionB: "Faridabad, Gurugram, and Ghaziabad",
        optionC: "Varanasi and Patna",
        correctAnswer: "Faridabad, Gurugram, and Ghaziabad",
      },
      {
        question: "Where does the President of India live in Delhi?",
        optionA: "South Block",
        optionB: "Rashtrapati Bhavan",
        optionC: "Lok Sabha",
        correctAnswer: "Rashtrapati Bhavan",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the beautiful gardens at Rashtrapati Bhavan?",
        optionA: "Mughal Gardens",
        optionB: "Amrit Udhyan",
        optionC: "Lotus Gardens",
        correctAnswer: "Mughal Gardens",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the highest brick minaret in the world located in Delhi?",
        optionA: "Taj Mahal",
        optionB: "India Gate",
        optionC: "Qutub Minar",
        correctAnswer: "Qutub Minar",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the main language spoken in Delhi, alongside Hindi and Punjabi?",
        optionA: "Tamil",
        optionB: "English",
        optionC: "Marathi",
        correctAnswer: "English",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Delhi is the largest metropolis in India. It lies on the west of the river __________.",
        optionA: "Ganges",
        optionB: "Brahmaputra",
        optionC: "Yamuna",
        correctAnswer: "Yamuna",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Delhi is bordered by Uttar Pradesh in the east and __________ on the other three sides.",
        optionA: "Punjab",
        optionB: "Haryana",
        optionC: "Rajasthan",
        correctAnswer: "Haryana",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Mughal emperor Shah Jahan built his capital at Delhi and called it __________.",
        optionA: "Kolkata",
        optionB: "Delhi",
        optionC: "Shahjahanabad",
        correctAnswer: "Shahjahanabad",
      },
      {
        question:
          "New Delhi was built by the __________ when they shifted their capital from Kolkata to Delhi.",
        optionA: "Mughals",
        optionB: "British",
        optionC: "French",
        correctAnswer: "British",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The National Capital Territory of Delhi incorporates satellite cities of Faridabad, Gurugram, Ghaziabad, Noida, and other nearby __________.",
        optionA: "States",
        optionB: "Areas",
        optionC: "Towns",
        correctAnswer: "Areas",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The President of India lives in __________, which has beautiful gardens named Amrit Udhyan.",
        optionA: "South Block",
        optionB: "Rashtrapati Bhavan",
        optionC: "Lok Sabha",
        correctAnswer: "Rashtrapati Bhavan",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The office of the Prime Minister of India is in the __________.",
        optionA: "North Block",
        optionB: "South Block",
        optionC: "Central Vista",
        correctAnswer: "South Block",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Qutub Minar is the highest brick minaret in the world, and it is located in __________.",
        optionA: "Red Fort",
        optionB: "India Gate",
        optionC: "Delhi",
        correctAnswer: "Delhi",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Delhi has an extreme climate, with very hot summers and very cold winters. In summer, hot dry winds called __________ blow.",
        optionA: "Breeze",
        optionB: "Loo",
        optionC: "Monsoon",
        correctAnswer: "Loo",
      },
      {
        question:
          "People of Delhi enjoy all types of food, such as South Indian, Chinese, Punjabi, and __________.",
        optionA: "Mexican",
        optionB: "Italian",
        optionC: "Japanese",
        correctAnswer: "Italian",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Delhi is the largest metropolis in India.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Delhi lies on the east of the river Yamuna.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "New Delhi was built by the British when they shifted their capital from Kolkata to Delhi.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Delhi has an extreme climate, with moderate temperatures throughout the year.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Delhi is a monolingual city, where only Hindi is spoken.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "All the important offices and residences of the Government of India are located in Delhi.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Delhi has many historical and modern monuments, including the Eiffel Tower.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Delhi is a landlocked city without any access to the sea.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Delhi is well connected with all parts of the country by roadways, railways, and airways.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The main language spoken in Delhi is French.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
